In this video
we'll learn the 3 basic steps on building apps
We call it 'ADD'
appearance, details, and debug
Here
we'll use the simple YouTube Downloader app as an example
First of all, we'll deal with the look
That'll be handled in the layout section
You're very lucky
coz you can download a ready-to-view template on Github
If you wanna dig deep on how to do it
feel free to watch the episode 2 and 3
Once you've designed the app's layout
you need to fill in the details
In our YouTube Downloader app
there're 2 basic functions
You can refer to episode 3 and 4
if you wanna know in-and-out how we do this
Throughout the process
you'll for sure encounter errors
That's the tedious part of debugging
That's episode 5 and 6
Finally
you'll learn how to convert the finished script to an actual app